Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XII: Energy Issues, undated, 1964-1982
  - National
    - Metropolitan Area Housing Alliance Utilities Coalition, 1977 (Box 79:, Folder 2902)
    - Multi-State Home Heating Oil Programs, 1979-1980 (Box 79:, Folder 2903)
    - Municipal Utilities, 1973 (Box 79:, Folder 2904)
    - National Center for Resource Recovery (Box 79:, Folder 2905)
    - National Conference: Solid Waste (Box 79:, Folder 2906)
    - National Economic Alternative Source Activists (Box 80:, Folder 2907)
    - National Energy Conservation Policy Act: Weatherization Programs (Box 80:, Folder 2908)
    - National Energy Policy, 1971-1972 (Box 80:, Folder 2909)
    - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1977 (Box 80:, Folder 2910-2911)
    - New England/New York Utilities (Box 80:, Folder 2912)
    - New England Power, 1969-1972 (Box 80:, Folder 2913)
    - New England Power Exchange, 1970-1973 (Box 80:, Folder 2914)
    - New York (Box 80:, Folder 2915)
    - New York Power Pool (Box 80:, Folder 2916)
    - Newsletters (Box 80:, Folder 2917)
    - Nuclear Energy: Mobilization for Survival, 1978 (Box 80:, Folder 2918)
    - Nuclear Power
      - General Information, 1975-1978 (Box 80:, Folder 2919-2922)
      - New England Coalition, 1974-1976 (Box 80:, Folder 2923-2925)
      - Plant Problems, 1975-1978 (Box 80:, Folder 2926)
      - Publications, 1978 (Box 80:, Folder 2927)
      - Radioactive Waste, 1978 (Box 80:, Folder 2928)
    - Occupational Safety: Labor Department Information, 1969-1971 (Box 80:, Folder 2929)
    - Occupational Safety and Health Act (OSHA), 1970-1973 (Box 80:, Folder 2930-2933)
    - OSHA and Small Business (Box 80:, Folder 2934)
    - OSHA; Toxic Substances, 1975-1977 (Box 80:, Folder 2935-2936)
    - Office of Emergency Preparedness, 1973 (Box 80:, Folder 2937)
    - Office of Energy Policy, 1973 (Box 80:, Folder 2938)
    - Office of Policy and Management (Box 80:, Folder 2939)
    - Oil and Gas, 1973 (Box 80:, Folder 2940-2941)
    - Oil Recycling (Box 80:, Folder 2942)
    - Oil Shortage (Box 80:, Folder 2943)
    - Oregon Department of Energy Plans (Box 80:, Folder 2944)
    - Other States (Box 80:, Folder 2945)
    - Peak Load (Box 80:, Folder 2946)
    - Power Demands, 1969 (Box 81:, Folder 2947)
    - Power Grid, 1973 (Box 81:, Folder 2948)
    - Power Siting, 1970-1973 (Box 81:, Folder 2.949295E7)
    - Press: Solid Waste (Box 81:, Folder 2951)
    - Private Utilities, 1972 (Box 81:, Folder 2952)
    - Promotional Practices, 1972 (Box 81:, Folder 2953)
    - Promotional Rates, 1970-1972 (Box 81:, Folder 2954)
    - Public Power: New York and Arizona, 1976-1977 (Box 81:, Folder 2955)
    - Regulatory Process: National (Box 81:, Folder 2956)
    - Reports on Shortage, 1979 (Box 81:, Folder 2957)
    - Residential Utility Consumer Action Group (RUCAG) (Box 81:, Folder 2958)
    - Resource Conservation and Recovery Act (RCRA), 1976 (Box 81:, Folder 2959-2960)
    - Resource Recovery Demonstrated (Box 81:, Folder 2961)
    - Resource Recovery Grants (Box 81:, Folder 2962)
    - Resource Recovery Summary (Box 81:, Folder 2963)
    - Restriction on Natural Gas, 1976-1977 (Box 81:, Folder 2964)
    - Rhode Island (Box 81:, Folder 2965)
    - Source Separation (Box 81:, Folder 2966)
    - Telephone Companies: Legislation, 1977-1978 (Box 81:, Folder 2967)
    - Tidal/Ocean Power (Box 82:, Folder 2968)
    - U.S. Department of Energy: Monthly Reviews Utilities (Box 82:, Folder 2969)
      - Newsletters, Other States, 1978 (Box 82:, Folder 2970)
      - Rate Structure (Box 82:, Folder 2971)
    - Vermont (Box 82:, Folder 2972)
    - Waste Works (Box 82:, Folder 2973)
    - Wasted Gas (Box 82:, Folder 2974)
    - Wind Power (Box 82:, Folder 2975)
    - Wood Power (Box 82:, Folder 2976)
  - Connecticut
    - Air Pollution, 1971-1972 (Box 83:, Folder 2977)
    - Building Codes, 1977-1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2978-2979)
    - Canaan Mountain (Box 83:, Folder 2980)
    - Coalition Mailing List (Box 83:, Folder 2981)
    - Colchester Case (Box 83:, Folder 2982)
    - Community Labor Alliance, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2983)
    - CT Energy Advisory Board (CEAB) (Box 83:, Folder 2984)
    - CCAG
      - Coordinators Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 83:, Folder 2985-2986)
      - Energy Organizing Ideas, 1977-1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2987-2989)
      - Fund Raising Reports, 1979 (Box 83:, Folder 2990)
      - Information on Issues, 1977 (Box 83:, Folder 2991)
      - Information Requests, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2992)
      - Originals, Memoranda, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2993)
      - Organizational Material, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2994-2995)
      - Proposal to List Foundation, 1977 (Box 83:, Folder 2996)
      - Staff Meetings, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2997)
      - Testimony, Pre-1975 (Box 83:, Folder 2998)
      - Utilities campaign, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 2999)
    - CT Citizens/Labor Energy Coalition (C/LEC) (Box 83:, Folder 3000-3002)
    - CT Conflict Resolution (Box 83:, Folder 3003)
    - CT Economic Alternative Sources Activists (Box 83:, Folder 3004)
    - CT Energy Agency (Box 83:, Folder 3005)
    - CT Energy Coalition (Box 83:, Folder 3006)
    - CT Energy Conservation Group (Box 83:, Folder 3007)
    - CT Fuel Purchasing (Box 83:, Folder 3008)
    - CT Gas and Water Companies (Box 83:, Folder 3009)
    - CT Home Energy Assistance Plan (Box 83:, Folder 3010)
    - CT Landfill Areas (Box 83:, Folder 3011)
    - Connecticut Light and Power Company, 1978 (Box 83:, Folder 3012-3013)
    - CT Miscellaneous (Box 83:, Folder 3014)
    - CT State Energy Conservation (Box 84:, Folder 3015-3016)
    - CT Utilities Energy Conservation Proposal (Box 84:, Folder 3017)
    - CT DEP Hay Unit Information (Box 84:, Folder 3018)
    - CT Residential Conservation Program (Box 84:, Folder 3019)
    - East Hartford Energy Report (Box 84:, Folder 3020)
    - Energy Policy (Box 84:, Folder 3021)
    - Energy Conservation (Box 84:, Folder 3022)
    - Energy Legislation, 1980 (Box 84:, Folder 3023)
    - Environmental Impact, 1970-1973 (Box 84:, Folder 3024)
    - Fair Rate Plan for Electricity, 1978 (Box 84:, Folder 3025)
    - FERC: CL&P/HELCO (Box 84:, Folder 3026)
    - Fitzpatrick/White Residential Assistance Program (Box 84:, Folder 3027)
    - Fuel Cell Energy (Box 84:, Folder 3028)
    - Fuel Oil (Box 84:, Folder 3029)
    - Gasoline Tax (Box 84:, Folder 3030)
    - Governor Grasso's Winter Energy Plan, 1979 (Box 84:, Folder 3031)
    - Grant Proposal 208 (Box 84:, Folder 3032-3039)
    - Grant Proposal 208 (Box 85:, Folder 3040-3041)
    - Grants (Box 85:, Folder 3042)
    - HELCO (CL&P), 1976-1979 (Box 85:, Folder 3043)
    - Hartford Process Report (Box 85:, Folder 3044)
    - Home Heating Oil Price Increase (Box 85:, Folder 3045)
    - Home Heating Oil Shortage, 1973 (Box 85:, Folder 3046)
    - Insulation
      - Legislation, 1977 (Box 85:, Folder 3047)
      - Background for Booklet (Box 85:, Folder 3048)
    - Intervention/Protest (Box 85:, Folder 3049)
    - Issue Analysis, 1976-1977 (Box 85:, Folder 3050)
    - Land Use, 1974 (Box 85:, Folder 3051)
    - Legislation, 1976-1978 (Box 85:, Folder 3052-3056)
    - Legislative Fact Sheet, 1977 (Box 85:, Folder 3057)
    - Life Cycle Coasting Act, 1977-1978 (Box 85:, Folder 3058)
    - Liquid Waste Conversion (LIQWACON) (Box 85:, Folder 3059)
    - Low Income Energy Legislation, 1979-1980 (Box 85:, Folder 3060)
    - Low Income Planning Agency, 1979 (Box 85:, Folder 3061)
    - Meter Reading Campaign, 1977-1978 (Box 85:, Folder 3062-3064)
    - Northeast Utilities
      - General, 1977 (Box 85:, Folder 3065-3067)
      - Annual Reports, 1969-1970 (Box 85:, Folder 3067)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 85:, Folder 3069)
      - Data (Box 85:, Folder 3070)
      - Media Campaign (Box 85:, Folder 3071)
      - Rate Hike (Box 85:, Folder 3072)
      - Research Prep Materials (Box 85:, Folder 3073)
      - Stock Certificate (Box 85:, Folder 3074)
      - Testimony to PREC and PUCA, 1978 (Box 85:, Folder 3075)
    - Norwich Sewer Problem, 1974-1978 (Box 85:, Folder 3076)
    - Occupational Safety, 1973 (Box 86:, Folder 3077)
    - OSHA, 1973 (Box 86:, Folder 3078-3079)
    - OSHA Evaluation Report, 1975 (Box 86:, Folder 3080)
    - Organizing (Box 86:, Folder 3081)
    - Peak Load (Box 86:, Folder 3082-3083)
    - P.I.F. Program, 1977-1978 (Box 86:, Folder 3084-3085)
    - Plainfield-Moosup Case (Box 86:, Folder 3086)
    - Plainfield Toxic Wastes (Box 86:, Folder 3087)
    - Power Facility Evaluation Council (PFEC), 1975 (Box 86:, Folder 3088)
    - Power Siting Task Force, 1971 (Box 86:, Folder 3089)
    - Public Act 79-362 (Box 86:, Folder 3090)
    - Public Utilities Commission (PUC) (Box 86:, Folder 3091-3092)
    - Public Utility Control Authority (PUCA) (Box 86:, Folder 3093-3097)
    - Rate Hike, 1972 (Box 86:, Folder 3098)
    - Rates, 1973 (Box 86:, Folder 3099)
    - Regulated Activities and Energy, 1977 (Box 86:, Folder 3100-3101)
    - Relevant News Items (Box 86:, Folder 3102)
    - Review of Public Participation: Solid Waste (Box 86:, Folder 3103)
    - Rocky Hill Case (Box 86:, Folder 3104)
    - Rocky River Realty Company, 1970 (Box 86:, Folder 3105)
    - Security Exchange Commission (SEC) (Box 86:, Folder 3106)
    - Seymour Case (Box 86:, Folder 3107)
    - Sherman Case (Box 86:, Folder 3108)
    - Solid Wastes Management Bill (Box 86:, Folder 3109)
    - Solid Wastes Maps (Box 86:, Folder 3110)
    - State Emergency Energy Program (Box 86:, Folder 3111)
    - Swift and Sons, 1977 (Box 86:, Folder 3112)
    - Telephone Companies
      - Guilford Phone Tolls, 1977-1978 (Box 86:, Folder 3113)
      - SNET Docket, 1978 (Box 86:, Folder 3114)
    - "Toll Free Now", 1977-1978 (Box 86:, Folder 3115-3116)
    - United Illuminating (Box 87)
      - Rate Hike Protest, 1978 (Box 87:, Folder 3117)
      - Rate Hick Protest, Fairfield, 1978 (Box 87:, Folder 3118)
      - Rate Hike Protest, New Haven, 1978 (Box 87:, Folder 3119)
      - Testimony of J. Stutz (Box 87:, Folder 3120)
    - Utility Shutoffs (Box 87:, Folder 3121)
    - Utilities
      - Advertising (Box 87:, Folder 3122-3123)
      - Gas and Electric Rate Schedule (Box 87:, Folder 3124)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 87:, Folder 3125)
      - Shutoffs, 1978 (Box 87:, Folder 3126)
    - Waste as Fuel (Box 87:, Folder 3127)
    - Waste Hunt Project
      - Windmills in Greenwich, 1978 (Box 87:, Folder 3128)
      - Winterization, 1977 (Box 87:, Folder 3129)
      - Xenergy Report (Box 87:, Folder 3130)
  - Insulation
    - Cellulose/Asbestos, 1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3131)
    - Fiberglass, 1971-1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3132-3134)
    - Formaldehyde Foam, 1976 (Box 88:, Folder 3135)
    - Pipe Insulation, 1974-1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3136)
    - Press Releases, 1977-1978 (Box 88:, Folder 3137)
    - Public Meeting on Home Insulation, 1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3138)
    - Retailer Questionnaires, 1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3139)
    - Saving Money by Insulating, 1974-1977 (Box 88:, Folder 3140)
    - Urethane Foam, 1977-1978 (Box 88:, Folder 3141)
  - Solar
    - Advertising (Box 89:, Folder 3142)
    - Applications for Solar Energy, 1976-1977 (Box 89:, Folder 3143-3145)
    - Canvass Materials, 1978 (Box 89:, Folder 3146)
    - Conferences/Courses on Solar Technology, 1977-1979 (Box 89:, Folder 3147-3157)
    - CT Solar Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 89:, Folder 3158-3167)
    - CT Solar Systems (Box 89:, Folder 3168)
    - Contacts, 1977-1978 (Box 89:, Folder 3169-3170)
    - Correspondence, 1978 (Box 89:, Folder 3171)
    - Economic Analysis of Solar Energy, 1980 (Box 89:, Folder 3172-3173)
    - General Information (Box 89:, Folder 3174)
    - Legislation, 1976-1979 (Box 89:, Folder 3175-3176)
    - Legislation, 1976-1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3177-3185)
    - Magazines, 1977-1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3186-3187)
    - Mailing Labels, 1978 (Box 90:, Folder 3188)
    - New Yorker Articles, 1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3189)
    - Newsletters, 1977-1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3190-3194)
    - Organizations (& Folders), 1978-1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3195)
    - Passive Solar Heating (Box 90:, Folder 3196)
    - Photoboltaics, 1977-1979 (Box 90:, Folder 3197)
    - Solar Equipment (Box 90:, Folder 3198)
    - Sun Day, 1978 (Box 90:, Folder 3199-3201)
    - Utilities, 1976-1978 (Box 90:, Folder 3202-3203)
  - Nuclear
    - Accident: 3 Mile Island (Box 91:, Folder 3204)
    - Active File, 1978 (Box 91:, Folder 3205)
    - Activists Nationwide (Box 91:, Folder 3206)
    - Anti-Nuclear: State Legislation (Box 91:, Folder 3207)
    - Atomic Energy Commission Policy (Box 91:, Folder 3208)
    - Breeder Reactor (Box 91:, Folder 3209-3210)
    - Business/Market (Box 91:, Folder 3211)
    - CCAG: Nuclear Power (Box 91:, Folder 3212)
    - Connecticut Nuclear Power Evaluation Council (Box 91:, Folder 3213)
    - Connecticut Radiation Transport Permits (Box 91:, Folder 3214)
    - Correspondence (Box 91:, Folder 3215)
    - Decommissioning Issues (Box 91:, Folder 3216)
    - Economics (Box 91:, Folder 3217-3219)
    - Environmental Impact (Box 91:, Folder 3220)
    - Evacuation Plans (Box 91:, Folder 3221)
    - Fusion (Box 91:, Folder 3222)
    - General Overview (Box 91:, Folder 3223)
    - Information, General (Box 91:, Folder 3224)
    - International (Box 91:, Folder 3225)
    - International Development (Box 91:, Folder 3226)
    - Legislation (Box 91:, Folder 3227-3230)
    - Millstone (Box 91:, Folder 3231-3237)
    - Native Americans and Nukes (Box 91:, Folder 3238)
    - New England Activists (Box 91:, Folder 3239)
    - New London Radiation Transport Ban (Box 91:, Folder 3240)
    - Non-Nuclear Sources of Radiation (Box 91:, Folder 3241)
    - Northeast (Box 91:, Folder 3242)
    - Northeast Utilities (Box 92:, Folder 3243)
    - Nuclear Plant Licensing (Box 92:, Folder 3244)
    - Nuclear Power Evaluation Council (NPEC) (Box 92:, Folder 3245)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Policy (Box 92:, Folder 3246)
    - Offshore Building (Box 92:, Folder 3247)
    - Peace/War Connection (Box 92:, Folder 3248)
    - Politics (Box 92:, Folder 3249)
    - Position Papers (Box 92:, Folder 3250)
    - Price Anderson Act (Box 92:, Folder 3251-3252)
    - Pro-Nuke Position (Box 92:, Folder 3253)
    - Public Opinion (Box 92:, Folder 3254)
    - Public Utilities Control Authority (PUCA) (Box 92:, Folder 3255-3256)
    - Radiation (Box 92:, Folder 3257-3259)
    - Reactor Safety (Box 92:, Folder 3260)
    - Real Estate Values (Box 92:, Folder 3261)
    - Regulations (Box 92:, Folder 3262)
    - Reprocessing (Box 92:, Folder 3263)
    - Safety (Box 92:, Folder 3264-3273)
    - Silkwood, Karen (Box 92:, Folder 3274-3275)
    - Sociological Impact (Box 92:, Folder 3276)
    - Transportation: Radioactive Materials (Box 92:, Folder 3277)
    - Uranium Fuel Cycle (Box 92:, Folder 3278)
    - Uranium Mining (Box 92:, Folder 3279)
    - Waste Management (Box 92:, Folder 3280-3281)
    - World Trade (Box 92:, Folder 3282)
    - Westinghouse Uranium Suit (Box 92:, Folder 3283)
  - Oil
    - Blue Hills energy Committee (Box 93:, Folder 3284)
    - Brookside Contracts (Box 93:, Folder 3285)
    - Conservation (Box 93:, Folder 3286)
    - Energy
      - Legislation, 1982 (Box 93:, Folder 3287)
      - Legislative Petitions, 1982 (Box 93:, Folder 3288)
      - Rally, 1982 November 17 (Box 93:, Folder 3289)
      - Rate Hikes, 1981-1982 (Box 93:, Folder 3290-3291)
      - Shut-off Information (Box 93:, Folder 3292)
    - Fuel Oil Co-op Information (Box 93:, Folder 3293)
    - Hartford Statistics (Box 93:, Folder 3294)
    - Jay's Research (Box 93:, Folder 3295-3298)
    - Motion to Dismiss Appeal (Box 93:, Folder 3299)
    - Northeast Utilities Materials (Box 93:, Folder 3300)
    - Oil Companies (Box 93:, Folder 3301-3302)
    - Oil Companies: Press (Box 94:, Folder 3303)
    - Oil Co-op
      - Committee (Box 94:, Folder 3304)
      - Membership Questionnaire (Box 94:, Folder 3305)
      - Originals (Box 94:, Folder 3306)
    - Oil/Gasoline Companies (Box 94:, Folder 3307)
    - Oil Price Survey (Box 94:, Folder 3308)
    - Oil Taxes
      - Pleading (Box 94:, Folder 3309-3311)
      - Legal Research (Box 94:, Folder 3312)
      - General (Box 94:, Folder 3313-3315)
    - Other Co-ops (Box 94:, Folder 3316)
    - Pass-through Memoranda (Box 94:, Folder 3317)
    - Political Action Committee (Box 94:, Folder 3318)
    - Texaco (Box 94:, Folder 3319)
  - Energy Publications
    - General
      - Alternate Sources of Energy, 1975-1979 (Box 95:, Folder 3320)
      - Alternate Sources of energy, 1977 (Box 95:, Folder 3321)
      - American Petroleum Institute, 1976 (Box 95:, Folder 3322)
      - Battelle Columbus Laboratories, 1977 (Box 95:, Folder 3323)
      - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1973 (Box 95:, Folder 3324)
      - Center for Energy Policy, 1976 (Box 95:, Folder 3325)
      - CCAG, 1973 (Box 95:, Folder 3326)
      - CT Air Conservation Commission, 1975 (Box 95:, Folder 3327)
      - CT Energy Extension Service, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3328)
      - Consumer Services, 1979 (Box 95:, Folder 3329)
      - Cooperative Extension Service, 1977-1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3330)
      - D.M. Publications, 1977 (Box 95:, Folder 3331)
      - Deepwater Oil (Box 95:, Folder 3332-3334)
      - Energy Conservation News, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3335)
      - Ford Foundation, 1974 (Box 95:, Folder 3336)
      - Hartford Conservancy, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3337)
      - Institute for Ecological Policies, 1979 (Box 95:, Folder 3338)
      - Living Alternatives, 1979 (Box 95:, Folder 3339)
      - Massachusetts Audubon, 1977 (Box 95:, Folder 3340)
      - New England Innovating, 1978-1980 (Box 95:, Folder 3341)
      - New Roots Periodicals, 1978-1979 (Box 95:, Folder 3342)
      - Northeast Utilities, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3343)
      - Old House Journal, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3344)
      - Popular Economics Press, 1976 (Box 95:, Folder 3345)
      - Street Talk, 1980 (Box 95:, Folder 3346)
      - United Auto Workers, 1978 (Box 95:, Folder 3347)
      - United Illuminating (Box 95:, Folder 3348)
      - Walt Disney Education Media (Box 95:, Folder 3349)
    - Nuclear
      - American Nuclear Society, 1976 (Box 96:, Folder 3350)
      - CCAG Script: "What in The World", 1970 (Box 96:, Folder 3351)
      - CT Yankee Emergency Plan, 1972 (Box 96:, Folder 3352)
      - Economics of Nuclear Power, 1975 (Box 96:, Folder 3353)
      - Evacuation Plans, the Achilles Heel of the Nuclear Industry, 1975 (Box 96:, Folder 3354)
      - Millstone Point Company Emergency Plan, 1972 (Box 96:, Folder 3355)
      - Millstone Point Company Emergency Plan Appendix, 1972 (Box 96:, Folder 3356)
      - Millstone Radiological Environmental Monitoring Program, 1975 (Box 96:, Folder 3357)
      - Nuclear Power Plant Safety, 1964-1975 (Box 96:, Folder 3358)
      - Nuclear Debate, 1974 (Box 96:, Folder 3359)
      - Nuclear Energy Pamphlets, 1974-1976 (Box 96:, Folder 3360)
      - Nuclear Energy Liability, 1976 (Box 96:, Folder 3361)
      - Nuclear Power Plant Safety, 1977-1979 (Box 96:, Folder 3362)
      - Power Plant Economics: Testimony, 1976 (Box 96:, Folder 3363)
      - Radiation and Health, 1966-1978 (Box 96:, Folder 3364)
    - Solar
      - AIA/Research Corp. (Box 96:, Folder 3365)
      - Center for Science in the Public, 1976 (Box 96:, Folder 3366)
      - Interest: Citizen Control (Box 96:, Folder 3367)
      - Community Services Administration, 1979 (Box 96:, Folder 3368)
      - Electric Power Research Institute, 1977 (Box 96:, Folder 3369)
      - George Washington University, 1978 (Box 96:, Folder 3370)
      - Honeywell, 1977 (Box 96:, Folder 3371)
      - Northeast Solar Energy Center, 1977 (Box 96:, Folder 3372)
      - Solar Action Office, 1978 (Box 96:, Folder 3373)
      - Solar Energies Industries Association, 1979 (Box 96:, Folder 3374)
      - Western Solar Utilization Network, 1979 (Box 96:, Folder 3375)
      - Millstone Nuclear Power Station (Box 97:, Folder 3376)
      - Millstone Nuclear Power Station 2 (Box 97:, Folder 3377)
      - Millstone Nuclear Power Station 3 (Box 97:, Folder 3378)
  - unspecified
    For further information on energy issues, see: Series I: Director's Records, Marc Caplan Files, Miles Rappoport Files, and Lenny Norwitz Files; Series III: Administrative Files; Series XVI: Subject Files; and Series XVII: 1992 Addendum.
- Series XIII: Utility Rate Cases, undated, 1970-1990s
  - 1974-1979
    - AT&T Consumer Communications Bill (Box 98:, Folder 3379)
    - Application: Southern CT Gas Company (Box 98:, Folder 3380)
    - Assessment of Load Forecasts and Resource Plan (Box 98:, Folder 3381)
    - Bethlehem Steel Corporation (Box 98:, Folder 3382)
    - Billing and Service (Box 98:, Folder 3383)
    - Billing Cards (Box 98:, Folder 3384)
    - Bills and Pamphlets, 1978 (Box 98:, Folder 3385)
    - Bloomfield (Box 98:, Folder 3386)
    - Book of Services (Box 98:, Folder 3387)
    - California Publications (Box 98:, Folder 3388)
    - Canvass Information (Box 98:, Folder 3389)
    - Citizens Action Group News Releases (Box 98:, Folder 3390)
    - Citizens Action Group: Washington, D.C. (Box 98:, Folder 3391)
    - City of New Haven, Intervenor (Box 98:, Folder 3392)
    - Clippings: CCAG (Box 98:, Folder 3393)
    - Clippings: Utility (Box 98:, Folder 3394)
    - Cole, Susan: Thesis (Box 98:, Folder 3395)
    - Colorado Environmental Information (Box 98:, Folder 3396)
    - Colorado Rates (Box 98:, Folder 3397)
    - Conference Originals (Box 98:, Folder 3398)
    - Connecticut Citizen-Labor Energy Coalition (CLEC) (Box 98:, Folder 3399)
    - Connecticut Energy and Environmental Conferences (Box 98:, Folder 3400)
    - Connecticut Information (Box 98:, Folder 3401)
    - Connecticut Light & Power Company (Box 98:, Folder 3402-3407)
    - Connecticut Natural Gas (Box 99:, Folder 3408-3412)
    - Connecticut Publications (Box 99:, Folder 3413)
    - Connecticut Public Utilities Control Authority (PUCA), 1975-1979 (Box 99:, Folder 3414-3423)
    - Consumer Complaints (Box 100:, Folder 3424)
    - Consumer Council (Box 100:, Folder 3425)
    - Consumer Information (Box 100:, Folder 3426)
    - Consumer Participation (Box 100:, Folder 3427)
    - Cos Cob Plant (Box 100:, Folder 3428)
    - Court of Common Please, 1977 (Box 100:, Folder 3436)
    - D.C. Rates (Box 100:, Folder 3437)
    - East Hartford CAG (Box 100:, Folder 3438)
    - Electric Utility Policy Issues (Box 100:, Folder 3439)
    - Electric Utility Rate Design (Box 100:, Folder 3440)
    - Energy Assistance (Box 100:, Folder 3441)
    - Energy Conservation (Box 100:, Folder 3442-3444)
    - Energy Conservation Project (Box 100:, Folder 3445)
    - Energy Consumer Workshop (Box 101:, Folder 3446)
    - Energy Growth and the Environment (Box 101:, Folder 3447)
    - Energy: Miscellaneous (Box 101:, Folder 3448)
    - Energy Training Conference (Box 101:, Folder 3449-3450)
    - Environment/Energy (Box 101:, Folder 3451)
    - Estimated Billing (Box 101:, Folder 3452-3455)
    - Federal Energy Administration (FEA) Rate Designs (Box 101:, Folder 3456)
    - Fuel Adjustment (Box 101:, Folder 3457-3459)
    - Fuel Adjustment Clause (FAC) (Box 101:, Folder 3460-3466)
    - Gas (Box 101:, Folder 3467)
    - General Conservation Project (Box 101:, Folder 3468)
    - General Electric, 1976 (Box 101:, Folder 3469-3470)
    - General Gas (Box 101:, Folder 3471)
    - Georgia Rates (Box 101:, Folder 3472)
    - Greater Hartford Utility Coalition (GHUC) (Box 101:, Folder 3473-3474)
    - Hartford Electric Light Company (HELCO), 1977-1978 (Box 102:, Folder 3475)
    - Haymarket (Box 102:, Folder 3476)
    - Invitations (Box 102:, Folder 3477)
    - Legal Notices, 1978-1979 (Box 102:, Folder 3478)
    - Legislation (Box 102:, Folder 3479)
    - Legislature, 1979 (Box 102:, Folder 3480)